A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Henry Carter Stuart, 1874-1918 (bulk 1914-1917)
Library of Virginia
- Executive Papers of Governor Henry Carter Stuart, 1874-1918 (bulk 1914-1917)., Extent: 32.70 cubic feet (72 boxes).
  - Requests for Publications
    - 1916 June-Oct. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - 1916 Nov.-Dec. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 1917 Jan.-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - 1917 May-Nov. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - 1918 Jan. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Requisition Accounts
    - 1914-1915 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Requisitions
    - 1914 Feb.-May (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - 1914 June-Oct. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - 1914 Nov.-Dec. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - 1915 Jan.-April (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - 1915 May-Sept. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - 1915 Oct.-Dec. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - 1916 Jan.-Aug. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - 1916 Sept.-Dec. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - 1917 Jan.-May (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - 1917 June-Sept. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - 1917 Oct.-Dec. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - 1918 Jan. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Reserve Bank, 1914-1916 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Resignations, 1914-1917 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Resolutions Transmitted, 1916 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Respites Granted and Applied for, 1916 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Rewards
    - 1914 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - 1915 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - 1916 Jan.-June (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - 1916 July-Dec. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - 1917 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg, & Potomac Railroad, 1915-1917 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Roads
    - 1914 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - 1915 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - 1916 Jan.-Sept. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - 1916 Oct.-Dec. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - 1917 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - 1918 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Rolling Stock Bill, 1912-1914 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Rural Credits, 1915-1917 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco Trip, 1915 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - School Superintendents
    - 1914 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 1915-1917 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Second Auditor, 1914-1917 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Session of 1916
    - 1914-1915 Oct. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - 1915 Nov.-1916 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Session of 1918
    - 1916 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - 1917 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Sinking Fund, 1874-1845 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Smithfield Light and Power Company, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Southern Commercial Congress
    - 1914-1915 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - 1916 Feb.-Nov. 27 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - 1916 Nov 28.-Dec. 5 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - 1916 Dec. 6-22 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - 1917 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Southwestern State Hospital, 1914-1917 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Special Elections, 1914, 1918 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Special Session of 1915, 1914-1915 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, 1914-1917 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Staff
    - 1913 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 1914 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - 1915 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Star-Spangled Banner Celebration, 1914 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - State Auditing Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - State Board of Accountancy, 1914-1917 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - State Board of Agriculture, 1914-1917 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - State Board of Charities & Corrections, 1914-1917 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - State Board of Dental Examiners
    - 1914-1916 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - 1917 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - State Board of Education
    - 1914 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - 1915 Jan.-June (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - 1915 July-Dec. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - 1916 Jan.-April (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - 1916 May-Sept. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - 1916 Oct.-Dec. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - 1917 Jan.-May (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - 1917 June-Dec. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - 1918 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - State Board of Embalmers, 1914-1917 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - State Board of Examiner of Applicants for Admission to the Bar, 1914-1917 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - State Board of Examiners of Graduate Nurses, 1914-1917 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - State Board of Health, 1914-1917 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - State Board of Medical Examiners, 1911-1917 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - State Board of Pharmacy, 1911-1917 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - State Board of Review, 1917 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - State Board of Veterinary Examiners, 1911-1917 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1913-1917 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - State Debt, 1915-1917 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - State Exhibit, 1917 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - State Fair, 1914-1917 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - State Female Normal School - Farmville, 1914 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - State Female Normal School - Fredericksburg, 1913-1915 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - State Female Normal School - Harrisonburg, 1914 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - State Female Normal School - Radford, 1914-1917 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - State Game Commissioner, 1914 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - State Officers, 1916 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - State Prosecution
    - 1914-1915 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - 1916 Jan.-June (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - 1916 July-1917 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - State Treasurer, 1914-1917 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - State Veterinarian, 1912-1918 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Subscriptions, 1916 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Summer Normal School (Big Stone Gap, Va.), 1914 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Taxation, Report of the Special Joint Committee on
    - Chapters I-IV, 1914 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Chapters V-Appendix, 1914 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Tax Commission, 1914 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Tax Matters
    - 1914-1915 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - 1916 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - 1917 Jan.-May (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 1917 June-Dec. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - 1918 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Taylor, Elvira Bruce, 1917-1918 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Triple Island Gun Club, ca. 1910-1914 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - University of Virginia
    - 1913-1915 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Valley Turnpike Company, 1914-1917 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Veto Matters, 1914-1916 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Anti-Tuberculosis Association, 1914-1917 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Home and Industrial School for Girls
    - 1910-1915 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Military Institute
    - 1913-1915 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Normal and Industrial Instutite (Petersburg, Va.), 1914-1916 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Normal School Board
    - 1914 March-April (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - 1914 May-June (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 1914 July-1917 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute
    - 1912-1915 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Road Builders' Association, 1917 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Virginia State Epileptic Colony, 1914-1917 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Vocational Education, 1917 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Washington Memorial, 1915-1917 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Washington (Martha) Will, 1914-1915 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Western State Hospital, 1914-1917 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - West Virginia Boundary, 1917 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - William and Mary College, 1914-1917 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Women's Co-Ordinate College, 1916 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Women's Suffrage, 1914-1917 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Workmen's Compensation Commission, 1914-1917 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - YMCA, 1916-1917 (Box 69, Folder 5)